<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau | Behavioural Science Research</title>
    <link>https://profgaelle.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau | Behavioural Science Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://profgaelle.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teaching and Learning Resources</title>
      <link>https://profgaelle.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://profgaelle.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my teaching resources collection. Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find materials from various workshops and courses focused on applied behavioural science.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;available-resources&#34;&gt;Available Resources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;workshops&#34;&gt;Workshops&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;circular-design-workshop/&#34;&gt;Circular Strategies Workshop: Redesigning Products for Sustainability&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;A hands-on workshop exploring circular design principles and product redesign&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Future workshops and resources will be added here.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-these-resources&#34;&gt;Using These Resources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These materials are shared to support learning and teaching in applied behavioural sciences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://profgaelle.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://profgaelle.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;peer-reviewed-research-outputs&#34;&gt;Peer-reviewed research outputs&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-press&#34;&gt;In press&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wei, Q., Van der Heijden, B. &amp;amp; Vallée-Tourangeau, G. (in press) Development and validation of the Chinese teacher sources of stress scale. &lt;em&gt;European Review of Applied Psychology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2024&#34;&gt;2024&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Juanchich, M., Oakley, C. M., Sayer, H., Holford, D. L., Bruine de Bruin, W., Booker, C., Chadborn, T., Vallee-Tourangeau, G., Wood, R. M., &amp;amp; Sirota, M. (2024). Vaccination invitations sent by warm and competent medical professionals disclosing risks and benefits increase trust and booking intention and reduce inequalities between ethnic groups. &lt;em&gt;Health Psychology&lt;/em&gt;, 43(10), 718-729. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001385&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001385&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>https://profgaelle.com/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://profgaelle.com/bio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau is a professor of Behavioural Science and Director of Research and Enterprise at Kingston Business School. She studied at Paris Ouest University (1998, MSc Social Psychology) and the University of Hertfordshire (2004, PhD) then was a lecturer at the Leeds University Business School (2001-2004) and the University of Toulouse (2004-2009) before joining Kingston University in 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her expertise lies in behavioural sciences and her research builds upon scientific reasoning and empirical evidence to explain what motivates human behaviour. She studies people’s choices and decisions as well as how to change behaviour. Her work contributes to better understand what influences decisions and creativity such as information design, the artefacts available in our environment, as well as individual motivational regulation needs such as the need for autonomy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoaTech&#39;s Rise</title>
      <link>https://profgaelle.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://profgaelle.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;: This article originally appeared on &lt;a href=&#34;https://incirclemedia.com&#34;&gt;GoaTech Insights&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GoaTech Insights has always been more than just another tech industry blog. Our mission is to be an integral part of the tech community, offering an in-depth and nuanced look at the latest developments in the field. Our ethos is encapsulated in our tagline: &amp;ldquo;Innovate and Inspire.&amp;rdquo; We believe that a tech news platform should not only be informative but also inspire its readers. We achieve this by being at the heart of the industry we cover. As a part of the dynamic tech ecosystem, GoaTech Insights is constantly evolving.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
