<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau | Behavioural Science Research</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau | Behavioural Science Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:39:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the years, my work has spanned different topics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-press&#34;&gt;In press&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wei, Q., Van der Heijden, B. &amp;amp; Vallée-Tourangeau, G. (in press) Development and validation of the Chinese teacher sources of stress scale. &lt;em&gt;European Review of Applied Psychology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2024&#34;&gt;2024&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Juanchich, M., Oakley, C. M., Sayer, H., Holford, D. L., Bruine de Bruin, W., Booker, C., Chadborn, T., Vallee-Tourangeau, G., Wood, R. M., &amp;amp; Sirota, M. (2024). Vaccination invitations sent by warm and competent medical professionals disclosing risks and benefits increase trust and booking intention and reduce inequalities between ethnic groups. &lt;em&gt;Health Psychology&lt;/em&gt;, 43(10), 718-729. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001385&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1037/hea0001385&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 13:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gaëlle Vallée-Tourangeau is a professor of Behavioural Science and Director of Research and Enterprise at Kingston Business School. She studied at Paris Ouest University (1998, MSc Social Psychology) and the University of Hertfordshire (2004, PhD) then was a lecturer at the Leeds University Business School (2001-2004) and the University of Toulouse (2004-2009) before joining Kingston University in 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her expertise lies in behavioural sciences and her research builds upon scientific reasoning and empirical evidence to explain what motivates human behaviour. She studies people’s choices and decisions as well as how to change behaviour. Her work contributes to better understand what influences decisions and creativity such as information design, the artefacts available in our environment, as well as individual motivational regulation needs such as the need for autonomy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
